{
    "subject": "resource/Svenska_H\u00f6garna",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Sweden",
    "human_readable": "Svenska H\u00f6garna is located in Sweden.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9523555636405945,
            "question": "Where is Svenska H\u00f6garna located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9320951104164124,
            "question": "Would you visit Svenska H\u00f6garna if you were in Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8474917411804199,
            "question": "In which country can you find Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7527540922164917,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7001508474349976,
            "question": "Is Svenska H\u00f6garna a natural landmark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6604751944541931,
            "question": "What is interesting about Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6272454857826233,
            "question": "What is the history of Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6142754554748535,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5289626121520996,
            "question": "Are there any famous people associated with Svenska H\u00f6garna?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34026652574539185,
            "question": "How would you describe Svenska H\u00f6garna to a friend?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Svenska H\u00f6garna is located in Sweden.",
            "html": "dbpedia_853_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people associated with Svenska H\u00f6garna?",
            "html": "dbpedia_853_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Svenska H\u00f6garna?",
            "html": "dbpedia_853_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Svenska H\u00f6garna?",
            "html": "dbpedia_853_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_853_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThis is because all the documents provided support the statement that \"Svenska H\u00f6garna\" is indeed a location in Sweden. The documents mention its location in Stockholm, Sweden, and provide geographical coordinates for the island."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references indicating that Svenska H\u00f6garna is located in Sweden, such as \"is_in: Stockholms l\u00e4n, Sweden\" and its detailed geographic location near other Swedish islands."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}